(Amy:)by sowing discord
in our relationship.
(Amy:)He's manipulating you
like he always does.
(Sheldon:)Wait, now, hang on.
(Sheldon:)You think he manipulates me?
(Amy:)All the time.
(Amy:)And he knew that as your girlfriend,
I wasn't gonna stand by
(Amy:)and let him bring a table
into your apartment.
I mean, a table? Come on!
(Sheldon:)It is hideous.
(Amy:)Well, thankfully,
I won't have to see it,
(Amy:)'cause I won't be your
girlfriend anymore.
(Amy:)Amy Farrah Fowler.
(Amy:)Why, yes, I would like
to take a survey.
(Leonard:)Wait.
(Sheldon:)You were really gonna stand by me
against the dining room table?
(Amy:)Of course I was.
(Leonard:)Wait.
(Sheldon:)How do I know that you're
not manipulating me right now?
(Amy:)I think if I were manipulating you,
you'd be smart enough to see it.
(Sheldon:)How do I know you're not saying that
as part of the manipulation?